serpbuddy.com 2017-03-18

# SerpBuddy - Keyword Rank Checker

### Privacy Policy

****  
Your Privacy is critically important to us. At SerpBuddy we have a few fundamental principles:  
We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.  
We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.  
We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.

Below is our Privacy Policy which incorporates these goals:

### Website Visitors

****  
Like most website operators, SerpBuddy collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. SerpBuddy’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how SerpBuddy’s visitors use its website. From time to time, SerpBuddy may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.  
SerpBuddy also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments our website. SerpBuddy only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below.  
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information  
Certain visitors to SerpBuddy’s websites choose to interact with SerpBuddy in ways that require SerpBuddy to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that SerpBuddy gathers depends on the nature of the interaction.  
Our web site is primarily designed to help you share prediction with the world. Most of the information you provide to us is information you are asking us to make public. This includes not only the prediction you share and the metadata provided with predictions but also the people you favorite, the prediction you mark as favorites or interact and many other bits of information. You should be careful about all information that will be made public by SerpBuddy, not just your predictions. 

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

****  
SerpBuddy discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on SerpBuddy behalf or to provide services available at SerpBuddy’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using SerpBuddy’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. SerpBuddy will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, SerpBuddy discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena or court order, or when SerpBuddy believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of SerpBuddy, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an SerpBuddy website and have supplied your email address, SerpBuddy may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with SerpBuddy and our products. We primarily use blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. SerpBuddy takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

****  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. SerpBuddy uses cookies to help SerpBuddy identify and track visitors, their usage of SerpBuddy website, and their website access preferences. SerpBuddy visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using SerpBuddy’s website, with the drawback that certain features of SerpBuddy’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Ads

****  
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by SerpBuddy and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

### Privacy Policy Changes

****  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, SerpBuddy may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in SerpBuddy’s sole discretion. SerpBuddy encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

Should you have any questions please use the contact form or you can also snail mail us at 4801 Lang Avenue NE, STE 110, Albuquerque, Bernalillo County, NM, 87109, USA, or even call us at 904-554-9693 during our normal business hours which are 9 AM to 5 PM Monday through Friday, -5:00 GMT.
